const cognitiveQuestionsData = {
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "8IPYL4L5",
            "choices": [
                "8YPIL4L5",
                "8IPYL5L4",
                "8ILYP4L5",
                "8IPYL4L5"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "8IPYL4L5"
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "OFL55JL4",
            "choices": [
                "5FL5OJL4",
                "OFL45JL5",
                "OFL5LJ54",
                "OFL55JL4"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "OFL55JL4"
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "BD2FCQKX",
            "choices": [
                "BD2FCQKX",
                "KD2FCQBX",
                "B2DFCQKX",
                "QD2FCBKX"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "BD2FCQKX"
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "WZPAPHBK",
            "choices": [
                "WZAPPHBK",
                "WZPAPHBK",
                "HZPAPWBK",
                "WPZAPHBK"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "WZPAPHBK"
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "question": "QHE1DLTU",
            "choices": [
                "QHE1DLTU",
                "QH1EDLTU",
                "QHE1DTLU",
                "QHT1DLEU"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "QHE1DLTU"
        },
        {
            "id": 6,
            "question": "P4INJ7CQ",
            "choices": [
                "P4INJ7CQ",
                "I4PNJ7CQ",
                "PI4NJ7CQ",
                "P4INJ7QC"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "P4INJ7CQ"
        },
        {
            "id": 7,
            "question": "2NTGVC09",
            "choices": [
                "2NT0VCG9",
                "2NTCVG09",
                "2NTGVC09",
                "2NCGVT09"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "2NTGVC09"
        },
        {
            "id": 8,
            "question": "K76BHDCQ",
            "choices": [
                "K76BHDCQ",
                "KC6BHD7Q",
                "K7HB6DCQ",
                "K67BHDCQ"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "K76BHDCQ"
        },
        {
            "id": 9,
            "question": "SOOXCYSL",
            "choices": [
                "OSOXCYSL",
                "SXOOCYSL",
                "SOCXOYSL",
                "SOOXCYSL"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "SOOXCYSL"
        },
        {
            "id": 10,
            "question": "IEQDEWZR",
            "choices": [
                "IWQDEEZR",
                "IEQDEWZR",
                "IEQDZWER",
                "IDQEEWZR"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "IEQDEWZR"
        },
        {
            "id": 11,
            "question": "EIX101FU",
            "choices": [
                "EIX101FU",
                "EIX011FU",
                "EIX1U1F0",
                "EIF101XU"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "EIX101FU"
        },
        {
            "id": 12,
            "question": "HXOPRW9F",
            "choices": [
                "HXO9RWPF",
                "HXOPRW9F",
                "HXOPFW9R",
                "PXOHRW9F"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "HXOPRW9F"
        },
        {
            "id": 13,
            "question": "V1TIK6EF",
            "choices": [
                "V1TIK6EF",
                "1VTIK6EF",
                "V1TIKE6F",
                "V1EIK6TF"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "V1TIK6EF"
        },
        {
            "id": 14,
            "question": "7STR33YD",
            "choices": [
                "7STRY33D",
                "7DTR33YS",
                "7STR33YD",
                "73TRS3YD"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "7STR33YD"
        },
        {
            "id": 15,
            "question": "3JQRQ162",
            "choices": [
                "2JQRQ163",
                "3JQ2Q16R",
                "RJQ3Q162",
                "3JQRQ162"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "3JQRQ162"
        },
        {
            "id": 16,
            "question": "U5C5O828",
            "choices": [
                "U5C5882O",
                "UOC55828",
                "85C5OU28",
                "U5C5O828"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "U5C5O828"
        },
        {
            "id": 17,
            "question": "L0IQO7RB",
            "choices": [
                "L0IQO7RB",
                "L0IQOBR7",
                "LOIQ07RB",
                "L0IQO7BR"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "L0IQO7RB"
        },
        {
            "id": 18,
            "question": "SFRI6Y9Y",
            "choices": [
                "SFRI6Y9Y",
                "9FRI6YSY",
                "SRFI6Y9Y",
                "YFRI6S9Y"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "SFRI6Y9Y"
        },
        {
            "id": 19,
            "question": "UT03I4MK",
            "choices": [
                "TU03I4MK",
                "UT03I4MK",
                "UT03IM4K",
                "IT03U4MK"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "UT03I4MK"
        },
        {
            "id": 20,
            "question": "LE8Z488T",
            "choices": [
                "L88Z4E8T",
                "LE8T488Z",
                "LE8Z488T",
                "LT8Z488E"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "LE8Z488T"
        },
        {
            "id": 21,
            "question": "U9NMQE29",
            "choices": [
                "U9MNQE29",
                "U9NMQE29",
                "U9NM9E2Q",
                "U9QMNE29"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "U9NMQE29"
        },
        {
            "id": 22,
            "question": "S9DXDHI3",
            "choices": [
                "S9DXDHI3",
                "39DXDHIS",
                "S9DXHDI3",
                "S9XDDHI3"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "S9DXDHI3"
        },
        {
            "id": 23,
            "question": "HV0WE7Z7",
            "choices": [
                "H70WEVZ7",
                "EV0WH7Z7",
                "HV0WE7Z7",
                "H70WE7ZV"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "HV0WE7Z7"
        },
        {
            "id": 24,
            "question": "6WW6KNXL",
            "choices": [
                "6WW6KNXL",
                "W6W6KNXL",
                "6WX6KNWL",
                "6WWLKNX6"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "6WW6KNXL"
        },
        {
            "id": 25,
            "question": "8887GFYV",
            "choices": [
                "88G78FYV",
                "8887GFYV",
                "7888GFYV",
                "8878GFYV"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "8887GFYV"
        },
        {
            "id": 26,
            "question": "5AFO7R6E",
            "choices": [
                "56FO7RAE",
                "5A7OFR6E",
                "EAFO7R65",
                "5AFO7R6E"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "5AFO7R6E"
        },
        {
            "id": 27,
            "question": "76GBWHIK",
            "choices": [
                "76IBWHGK",
                "76GBWKIH",
                "76GBWHIK",
                "7HGBW6IK"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "76GBWHIK"
        },
        {
            "id": 28,
            "question": "EV206MWV",
            "choices": [
                "EVV06MW2",
                "EV20M6WV",
                "EV206MWV",
                "EV206WMV"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "EV206MWV"
        },
        {
            "id": 29,
            "question": "9UT8L93S",
            "choices": [
                "93T8L9US",
                "9UT89L3S",
                "9UT8L93S",
                "9U98LT3S"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "9UT8L93S"
        },
        {
            "id": 30,
            "question": "UZU3HY6C",
            "choices": [
                "UZU3HY6C",
                "UZU3H6YC",
                "UZU6HY3C",
                "UZU36YHC"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "UZU3HY6C"
        },
        {
            "id": 31,
            "question": "83AJQH9E",
            "choices": [
                "83AJQH9E",
                "839JQHAE",
                "Q3AJ8H9E",
                "E3AJQH98"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "83AJQH9E"
        },
        {
            "id": 32,
            "question": "BPKX2JTG",
            "choices": [
                "B2KXPJTG",
                "BPKX2JTG",
                "GPKX2JTB",
                "BKPX2JTG"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "BPKX2JTG"
        },
        {
            "id": 33,
            "question": "4QNA8ILM",
            "choices": [
                "MQNA8IL4",
                "4QIA8NLM",
                "4QN8AILM",
                "4QNA8ILM"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "4QNA8ILM"
        },
        {
            "id": 34,
            "question": "G0WR0TVD",
            "choices": [
                "G00RWTVD",
                "G0RW0TVD",
                "G0WR0TVD",
                "GVWR0T0D"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "G0WR0TVD"
        },
        {
            "id": 35,
            "question": "C6A9L5MY",
            "choices": [
                "96ACL5MY",
                "C6L9A5MY",
                "CMA9L56Y",
                "C6A9L5MY"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "C6A9L5MY"
        },
        {
            "id": 36,
            "question": "0P4D8GSQ",
            "choices": [
                "0P4D8GSQ",
                "0P8D4GSQ",
                "0P4DQGS8",
                "0S4D8GPQ"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "0P4D8GSQ"
        },
        {
            "id": 37,
            "question": "SD73P838",
            "choices": [
                "SD73P838",
                "SD7338P8",
                "S873PD38",
                "SD7P3838"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "SD73P838"
        },
        {
            "id": 38,
            "question": "JJMYDMF5",
            "choices": [
                "JJMYDM5F",
                "JJMYDMF5",
                "J5MYDMFJ",
                "JMJYDMF5"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "JJMYDMF5"
        },
        {
            "id": 39,
            "question": "20BIHG8L",
            "choices": [
                "20BIHGL8",
                "G0BIH28L",
                "2B0IHG8L",
                "20BIHG8L"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "20BIHG8L"
        },
        {
            "id": 40,
            "question": "WR1XQZDT",
            "choices": [
                "ZR1XQWDT",
                "WR1XQZDT",
                "WR1QXZDT",
                "WR1TQZDX"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "WR1XQZDT"
        },
        {
            "id": 41,
            "question": "31QC204X",
            "choices": [
                "32QC104X",
                "31QC204X",
                "314C20QX",
                "31QX204C"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "31QC204X"
        },
        {
            "id": 42,
            "question": "T9NY3P8J",
            "choices": [
                "T9N3YP8J",
                "T9NY8P3J",
                "TN9Y3P8J",
                "T9NY3P8J"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "T9NY3P8J"
        },
        {
            "id": 43,
            "question": "6HYH468L",
            "choices": [
                "6HYH468L",
                "6YHH468L",
                "6HHY468L",
                "6HYHL684"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "6HYH468L"
        },
        {
            "id": 44,
            "question": "FD3YEBKY",
            "choices": [
                "YD3YEBKF",
                "FK3YEBDY",
                "FD3YBEKY",
                "FD3YEBKY"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "FD3YEBKY"
        },
        {
            "id": 45,
            "question": "AFPGG3F7",
            "choices": [
                "GFPAG3F7",
                "AFPGG3F7",
                "AFFGG3P7",
                "AFPG73FG"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "AFPGG3F7"
        },
        {
            "id": 46,
            "question": "MPXROX6I",
            "choices": [
                "MPXORX6I",
                "MPXROX6I",
                "MXXROP6I",
                "MPIROX6X"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "MPXROX6I"
        },
        {
            "id": 47,
            "question": "3EL5WGTY",
            "choices": [
                "3YL5WGTE",
                "35LEWGTY",
                "3EW5LGTY",
                "3EL5WGTY"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "3EL5WGTY"
        },
        {
            "id": 48,
            "question": "OWSHFP14",
            "choices": [
                "OSWHFP14",
                "OWSHFP41",
                "PWSHFO14",
                "OWSHFP14"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "OWSHFP14"
        },
        {
            "id": 49,
            "question": "J21CDCHB",
            "choices": [
                "J21CCDHB",
                "J21CDCHB",
                "JD1C2CHB",
                "J21DCCHB"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "J21CDCHB"
        },
        {
            "id": 50,
            "question": "4IUG7OZU",
            "choices": [
                "4I7GUOZU",
                "4IUG7OZU",
                "4GUI7OZU",
                "47UGIOZU"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "4IUG7OZU"
        }
    ]
};